<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>meditations on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/meditations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in meditations on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with 💚 by Mica, 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/meditations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bucket Full of Flowers: Philly Edition</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/106-abucketfullofflowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/106-abucketfullofflowers/</guid>
      <description>A couple of years ago, I wrote, what remains to this day, one of my favorite blog posts of all time, A Bucket Full of Fowers.
A hundred blogs and three years later, flowers remain a small tradition in our apartments. They were for the remainder of our life in Mexico; it continued while in Argentina, and now we pay patronage here in Philly. Flowers still bring me as much joy as ever, and I take care of them with the same devotion, changing their water every day, getting rid of unnecessary leaves, and throwing away the ones starting to wither.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being on the good side of statistics</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/104-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/104-covid/</guid>
      <description>Despite all the uncertainty surrounding COVID, we have sufficient evidence to show that death rates among young adults are pretty low. It is possibly even lower if the individual has no pre-existing conditions (like asthma or some auto-immune disease). But even with a death-rate of 0.1% is 500% more than the one we observe in the regular flu-season (0.02%).
I know I am on the good side of statistics. If, by any chance, I get COVID, there&amp;rsquo;s a big chance I end up having only mild symptoms and no severe, long-lasting effects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduate Mantra</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/103-dummest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/103-dummest/</guid>
      <description>From the dummest person in the class,the biggest piece on wisdom... You know what they call the dumbest person to graduate with a phd? Doctor. avocadontfckntalk2me
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best case for Atheism</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/101-atheism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/101-atheism/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;I believe in the scientific method, and in the scientific method if you cannot test a hypothesis then you cannot reach a meaningful conclusion that is true&amp;rdquo;
 Elon Musk
Interview with Alex Friedman</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regrouping</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/99-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/99-fall/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in the midst of our daily routine, we simply forget to breathe.
To breathe and look around us. To realize that we are exactly where we want to be. That all the work we are putting in will eventually pay off, the same way it paid off in the past, which got us to the place we are right now - drinking mate, thousand miles away from home, and going through my favorite season for the second time this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>battles</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/16-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/16-battles/</guid>
      <description>The Morning and I
A lesson I learned a long time ago:
Not all battles are worth fighting for. The hard part is choosing the correct ones
Like my hair this morning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decisions</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/15-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/15-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Life is a huge decision making process, everything revolving our lives was a decision taken at some point.
A big question is, what degree of freedom we have in our decisions? A few days ago this question was posted on our coffee break, and some people smarter than me stated there is no such thing as freewill, and that in this sense our brain does not really evaluate options, but the decision is already made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Togetherness</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/14-togetherness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/14-togetherness/</guid>
      <description>The Moment
The memory of the first time I thought ‘There might be something here’ is still crystal clear in my mind. It was an afternoon, after our half- failed Appalachian hiking, we both were reading minding our own business but being there for each other. I was with my Kindle with ‘Eating animals‘, he was with his hardcover of ‘Why Buddhism is True‘. I was laying on the couch, he was sitting on the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Them Cry</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/13-letthemcry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/13-letthemcry/</guid>
      <description>A perfect image of my mind today
Today’s morning was one of THOSE morning. You know, those type of mornings (sometimes it can last the whole day) where no matter what you are doing, you could always be doing something better.
When I was journaling, I wanted to study High Valyrian
When I was learning High Valyrian, I wanted to be at the 9am yoga class
When I decided I was not going to yoga in the morning but rather leave it for the afternoon, I wanted a coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bucket Full of Flowers</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/9-abucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/9-abucket/</guid>
      <description>‘On Sundays the office is closed’ or so my boyfriend thought one of the first weekends we were at Playa del Carmen. I had woken up early to go to the market to buy groceries and such, when I saw a small stand were they were selling flowers; huge beautiful yellow, white, orange flowers. I thought flowers would make home a much cheerful place to work so I decided to buy flowers for my boyfriend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Week of Blogging</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/8-aweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/8-aweek/</guid>
      <description>My first week of blogging is over and here are 7 highlights:
  According to people I write better than I talk (so imagine how I talk)
  It liberates your mind from random thoughts that keep appearing on a daily basis, it’s all about uncluttering
  Creating habits is easier when you are doing it with somebody else
  You can create a great unintended debate at dinnertime</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>