<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reflexions on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/reflexions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reflexions on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/reflexions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ñuhon geltītsos amāzigon jaelagan</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/19-iwmhb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/19-iwmhb/</guid>
      <description>page of ‘I Want my Hat back’ but Jon Klessen
After a week in which I experienced every flavor of thought available to mankind (anxiousness, sadness, hopelessness, happiness and anxiety again), I found the best way for coping with this fluctuating state of mind… simply re- read your favorite children’s book. The simplicity of it all gives you a great perspective of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>battles</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/16-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/16-battles/</guid>
      <description>The Morning and I
A lesson I learned a long time ago:
Not all battles are worth fighting for. The hard part is choosing the correct ones
Like my hair this morning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decisions</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/15-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/15-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Life is a huge decision making process, everything revolving our lives was a decision taken at some point.
A big question is, what degree of freedom we have in our decisions? A few days ago this question was posted on our coffee break, and some people smarter than me stated there is no such thing as freewill, and that in this sense our brain does not really evaluate options, but the decision is already made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Togetherness</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/14-togetherness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/14-togetherness/</guid>
      <description>The Moment
The memory of the first time I thought ‘There might be something here’ is still crystal clear in my mind. It was an afternoon, after our half- failed Appalachian hiking, we both were reading minding our own business but being there for each other. I was with my Kindle with ‘Eating animals‘, he was with his hardcover of ‘Why Buddhism is True‘. I was laying on the couch, he was sitting on the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Them Cry</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/13-letthemcry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/13-letthemcry/</guid>
      <description>A perfect image of my mind today
Today’s morning was one of THOSE morning. You know, those type of mornings (sometimes it can last the whole day) where no matter what you are doing, you could always be doing something better.
When I was journaling, I wanted to study High Valyrian
When I was learning High Valyrian, I wanted to be at the 9am yoga class
When I decided I was not going to yoga in the morning but rather leave it for the afternoon, I wanted a coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bucket Full of Flowers</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/9-abucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/9-abucket/</guid>
      <description>‘On Sundays the office is closed’ or so my boyfriend thought one of the first weekends we were at Playa del Carmen. I had woken up early to go to the market to buy groceries and such, when I saw a small stand were they were selling flowers; huge beautiful yellow, white, orange flowers. I thought flowers would make home a much cheerful place to work so I decided to buy flowers for my boyfriend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Week of Blogging</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/8-aweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/8-aweek/</guid>
      <description>My first week of blogging is over and here are 7 highlights:
  According to people I write better than I talk (so imagine how I talk)
  It liberates your mind from random thoughts that keep appearing on a daily basis, it’s all about uncluttering
  Creating habits is easier when you are doing it with somebody else
  You can create a great unintended debate at dinnertime</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>