<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addahna.com/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addahna.com/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Discarding - Book</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/the-art-of-discarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/the-art-of-discarding/</guid>
      <description>Like everyone else, I heard about this book after reading Marie Kondo&amp;rsquo;s book. We are about to move pretty soon and I need motivation and willingness to let things go. This book provided a lot of motivation for discarding, at times even a little bit too much.
Nagisa clearly states our underlying motivations for not getting rid of our possessions and how sooner or later stuff just ends up overflowing not only physical space but our mental space as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Project - Book</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/72-reviewthp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/72-reviewthp/</guid>
      <description>Often learn more from one person’s highly idiosyncratic experiences than I do from sources that detail universal principles or cite up-to-date studies. I find greater value in what specific individuals tell me worked for them than in any other kind of argument—and that’s true even when we seem to have nothing in common.
Gretchen Rubin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Happiness Project&amp;rdquo; is exactly what the title anticipates: a recollection of her journey through finding a greater sense of joy and happiness through small habit changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Gentleman in Moscow - book review</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/63-agim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/63-agim/</guid>
      <description>“if a man does not master his circumstances then he is bound to be mastered by them.”
   Count Alexander Ilyich Rostov   ![bingo]/addhana(/63-AGIM.jpg)
Hotel Metropol, Moscow, Russia (circa 1905). Source Wiki Commons
It is hard finding someone that does not recommend ‘A Gentleman in Moscow‘, from my mother-in-law to my boyfriend and Bill Gates, Count Alexander Ilyich Rostov seems to have earned a place in everyone’s heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ñuhon geltītsos amāzigon jaelagan</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/19-iwmhb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/19-iwmhb/</guid>
      <description>page of ‘I Want my Hat back’ but Jon Klessen
After a week in which I experienced every flavor of thought available to mankind (anxiousness, sadness, hopelessness, happiness and anxiety again), I found the best way for coping with this fluctuating state of mind… simply re- read your favorite children’s book. The simplicity of it all gives you a great perspective of life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>