<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>relationships on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://mica-92.github.io/tags/relationships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in relationships on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mica-92.github.io/tags/relationships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnecting</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/65-reconnecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/65-reconnecting/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I (finally) graduated from college. After years of hard work with countless hours with my but in the chairs and my nose between textbooks I made it over 5 years of intense work where summarized in a 40-minute presentation.
Many of my close friends gathered to see the whole thing unfold in youtube, and reading their comments and feeling their virtual presence had a nice comforting sensation in a time where the sense of isolation is the new norm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fasting</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/50-fasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/50-fasting/</guid>
      <description>Since Sunday I’ve began intermittent fasting.
I’m using a great app, Zero, to track the 16:8 cycle.
Chores have been distributed the following way during the past couple of weeks of quarantine:
Mica – lunch Ted – dinner Since Monday Ted asks me (anxiously) around noon when I’m going to take care of lunch. Because of the 16 hour fast window, lately it has been around 2 o’clock, failing to realize this fundamental truth about our new lunch schedule:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling quesosa</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/49-quesosa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/49-quesosa/</guid>
      <description>In the past months I went from being the happy state of singletown to the happy silly state of ‘Hey! This is my boyfriend. Have I told you he is the most amazing person in the world (yes, probably like a thousand times)
  Being in love is like that – silly, inexplicable
  It simply just happens
  Sometimes we do look for it a little bit under some random rocks we encounter in our journey</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multitasking</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/41-multitasking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/41-multitasking/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered my boyfriend can actually do two things at the same time.
Which ones, I rather not say</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Image</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/24-mentalimage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/24-mentalimage/</guid>
      <description>Time in Playa del Carmen is coming to an end. The next 10 days are fully occupied with traveling and DIY meditation retreats, so we decided take a day off and give one last visit technology-free visit of the year to our place in the world (La Zebra) .
My inner goal was to try to stay mindful all day (or at least most of it). So here are some mental highlights of the day:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 requests</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/21-2requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/21-2requests/</guid>
      <description>Me
‘I’m going for a walk. You will probably be in cloud nine when I come back, so please: 1. Leave me at least a third of the bed, 2. Don’t steal my pillow’
That’s me failing at the most basic requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Togetherness</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/14-togetherness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/14-togetherness/</guid>
      <description>The Moment
The memory of the first time I thought ‘There might be something here’ is still crystal clear in my mind. It was an afternoon, after our half- failed Appalachian hiking, we both were reading minding our own business but being there for each other. I was with my Kindle with ‘Eating animals‘, he was with his hardcover of ‘Why Buddhism is True‘. I was laying on the couch, he was sitting on the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October, 28th - a memoir</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/12-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/12-today/</guid>
      <description>Downward facing dog?
Today was a good days in many ways. I gave my first Spanish lesson, I’m seeing some extraordinary progress in my English student, tried the recipe for avocado dressing (without the basil), have some beautiful orange flowers in my coffee table, ate an amazing salad for lunch, continue improving on my High Valyrian, meditated (or I’m going to in a couple of minutes), had a breakfast- type dinner, cleaned the house (that’s looking so nice), organized the kitchen shelf, drank mate, tried a piece of plum tart from the bakery shop around the corner, wrote my dad his birthday card, mum sent me pictures of my granddad’s french play, talked to friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me too</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/4-metoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/blog/4-metoo/</guid>
      <description>Every night when I go to bed I kiss my boyfriend goodnight, look at him in the eyes and tell him ‘I love you, baby’, After what follows complete silence.
It’s been a little bit less than 2 months since I made that first statement driving through Virginia the day I decided I was going to loose my flight ticket to explore the perks of living in Mexico with someone I met on a plane.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>