<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mexico on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addahna.com/tags/mexico/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mexico on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addahna.com/tags/mexico/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>13 hour flight and counting</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/33-13hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/33-13hour/</guid>
      <description>The Andes
Last stop Lima. Final destination Buenos Aires. Estimation time 5.30 hours</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunrise &amp; coffee</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/32-sunrisecoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/32-sunrisecoffee/</guid>
      <description> The meaning of life is just to be alive. It is so plain and so obvious and so simple. And yet, everybody rushes around in a great panic as if it were necessary to achieve something beyond themselves
  Alan Watts
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Day</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/31-lastday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/31-lastday/</guid>
      <description>Last day in this wonderful place with the most beautiful skies in the world.
Going back home 🇦🇷</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Image</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/24-mentalimage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/24-mentalimage/</guid>
      <description>Time in Playa del Carmen is coming to an end. The next 10 days are fully occupied with traveling and DIY meditation retreats, so we decided take a day off and give one last visit technology-free visit of the year to our place in the world (La Zebra) .
My inner goal was to try to stay mindful all day (or at least most of it). So here are some mental highlights of the day:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dia de los Muetos</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/18-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/18-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Holidays like Día de los muertos (Halloween) make me feel an outsider of my own species.
Is not that I don’t like going out, but I just don’t feel such a strong feeling to connect with the masses in these kind of commercial holidays, probably just using them as an excuse to either eat a bunch of sugar in the form of hard candy or get dressed in an unusual, weird ‘likely to be regretted a couple of years from now’ way, and get drunk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Word Post</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/11-lazebra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/11-lazebra/</guid>
      <description>La Zebra, Tulum</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Enthusiast</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/6-naturalenthusiast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/6-naturalenthusiast/</guid>
      <description>I’m a natural enthusiast.
Wait! you never heard this before? Good, me neither and is because I just made this up. This is no psychological diagnose or anything of that sort is just the way I’ve always been and that I think, right now, is the main reason of a great distress in my head.
I think I’m going through a quarter-of-a-century kinda crisis. I wake up every morning not knowing what I am going to do or where I’m heading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Hunt</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/5-jobhunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/5-jobhunt/</guid>
      <description>After a couple months in low- season Playa del Carmen I came to the realization that life is harder than it seems. I never considered myself lucky with my past jobs (always grateful, never lucky) but after a month of trying to get a decent paycheck in Mexico I started believing I was. Being a full time student of an (yet) unfinished major for most of my adult life, working was never a top priority for me, so my past jobs were jobs that I performed to have some kind of personal income or to pay for that year’s vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>