<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with 💚 by Mica, 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>evermore</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/109-evermore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/109-evermore/</guid>
      <description>After writing my senior thesis under the influence of Lover
Living my first Penn semester with folklore on repeat.
Crying with the long pond sessions
evermore is the best way to share my return home. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StormAid</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/108-stormaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/108-stormaid/</guid>
      <description>In another chapter of Mica-Designs, a fellow graduate student ask me to help her design a logo for raising funds for a Hurricane Relief Fund for Central America.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on and off with these ones for the past couple of weeks, not really knowing what Nati wanted or finding sources of inspiration on Google. These are the ones I ended up picking for her :)
Gambit&amp;rsquo;s Front Page, here I go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franklin</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/107-franklin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/107-franklin/</guid>
      <description>As I observe Franklin every day, I wonder how something with such a strong character -with defined tastes and ways of communicating what he wants- not to be conscious?
For me, Frankie presents all the attributes by which I believe there&amp;rsquo;s a Mica. I have a distinct personality, erratic and highly emotional, and ways of expressing to the world who and how I am. And Franklin does too. His toolbox is different than mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bucket Full of Flowers: Philly Edition</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/106-abucketfullofflowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/106-abucketfullofflowers/</guid>
      <description>A couple of years ago, I wrote, what remains to this day, one of my favorite blog posts of all time, A Bucket Full of Fowers.
A hundred blogs and three years later, flowers remain a small tradition in our apartments. They were for the remainder of our life in Mexico; it continued while in Argentina, and now we pay patronage here in Philly. Flowers still bring me as much joy as ever, and I take care of them with the same devotion, changing their water every day, getting rid of unnecessary leaves, and throwing away the ones starting to wither.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Second Kind of Impossible</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/105-quasicrystals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/105-quasicrystals/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I had learned early on to pay close attention whenever an idea is dismissed as “impossible.” Most of the time, scientists are referring to something that is truly out of the question, like violating the conservation of energy or creating a perpetual motion machine. It never makes sense to pursue those kinds of ideas. But sometimes, an idea is judged to be “impossible” based on assumptions that could be violated under certain circumstances that have never been considered before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being on the good side of statistics</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/104-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/104-covid/</guid>
      <description>Despite all the uncertainty surrounding COVID, we have sufficient evidence to show that death rates among young adults are pretty low. It is possibly even lower if the individual has no pre-existing conditions (like asthma or some auto-immune disease). But even with a death-rate of 0.1% is 500% more than the one we observe in the regular flu-season (0.02%).
I know I am on the good side of statistics. If, by any chance, I get COVID, there&amp;rsquo;s a big chance I end up having only mild symptoms and no severe, long-lasting effects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduate Mantra</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/103-dummest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/103-dummest/</guid>
      <description>From the dummest person in the class,the biggest piece on wisdom... You know what they call the dumbest person to graduate with a phd? Doctor. avocadontfckntalk2me
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committee, maybe?</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/102-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/102-committee/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the best description I found on how to write an email to a prospect member of your graduate committee in the middle of a global pandemic:
&#34;Hey I just met you.And this is crazy.
But here&#39;s my number
Committee, maybe?&#34;
But the good news even with all that ackwardness 3 out of 5 have already accepted. One if from New Zealand :)
I&amp;rsquo;m counting on you Doug and Ileana!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best case for Atheism</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/101-atheism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/101-atheism/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;I believe in the scientific method, and in the scientific method if you cannot test a hypothesis then you cannot reach a meaningful conclusion that is true&amp;rdquo;
 Elon Musk
Interview with Alex Friedman</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post 100th! - Official</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/100/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/100/</guid>
      <description>The small things that make me feel part of a larger community. I&amp;rsquo;m so proud :)
EES Profile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regrouping</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/99-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/99-fall/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in the midst of our daily routine, we simply forget to breathe.
To breathe and look around us. To realize that we are exactly where we want to be. That all the work we are putting in will eventually pay off, the same way it paid off in the past, which got us to the place we are right now - drinking mate, thousand miles away from home, and going through my favorite season for the second time this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EES Logo</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/99-eeslogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/99-eeslogo/</guid>
      <description>The Earth and Environmental Science Department is holding a contest for its logo. I have so much fun doing these kinds of things I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop myself from participating.
These are my two contributions to the contest:
 #fingerscrossedThe colors I used are Penn&amp;rsquo;s colors accoridng to these guidelines. Penn Name Font – Perpetua or Traveling Typewriter (free font here). EES Font - National Park (free font link here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tipying</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/98-typingchallenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/98-typingchallenge/</guid>
      <description>Keybr Challenge • Keybr Profile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental note</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/96-mentalnote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/96-mentalnote/</guid>
      <description>HomonymsPotluck has nothing to do with pot.
 Potluck (noun) - a communal meal to which people bring food to share —usually used attributively
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 1st, 2020 - First Day</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/95-firstday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/95-firstday/</guid>
      <description>I survived my first day of graduate education.
Like Ted always says:
Life&#39;s good</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAing 2.0</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/94-taing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/94-taing/</guid>
      <description>This week has all been about moving to Philly and getting ready for the fall semester. As part of my graduate education, I have to TA for at least two semesters. I am thrilled about this new role. Teaching has always been something I wanted to give it a try, something that I could see my self doing as a career path along with being part of a research team. Before throwing us to the wolves, the school offered a two week TA training, and opposite to my expectations, I found the seminars very insightful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mood</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/93-mood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/93-mood/</guid>
      <description>And they called off the circus, burned the disco down
When they sent home the horses and the rodeo clowns
I&amp;rsquo;m still on that tightrope
I&amp;rsquo;m still trying everything to get you laughing at me
And I&amp;rsquo;m still a believer, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know why
I&amp;rsquo;ve never been a natural, all I do is try, try, try
I&amp;rsquo;m still on that trapeze
I&amp;rsquo;m still trying everything to keep you looking at me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Session One</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/92-writing-session-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/92-writing-session-one/</guid>
      <description>Today I started writting my first scientific paper :) The first one of many to come. I officially started making used of my Lic. prefix.
 I hit a &amp;gt;50wpm for the first time.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/91-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/91-28/</guid>
      <description>I just left behind a wonderful year, even with all the crazyness of the final months.
 Can&#39;t wait to see what 28 has under its sleeve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Things about today</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/90-3things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/90-3things/</guid>
      <description>#1 7 days.#2 Tomorrow: 28.
#3 Folklore is better with every listen.
&#39;Cause I knew you
Steppin&#39; on the last train
Marked me like a bloodstain, I
I knew you
Tried to change the ending
Peter losing Wendy, I
I knew you
Leavin&#39; like a father
Running like water, I
And when you are young, they assume you know nothing— Cardigan, Taylor Swift</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keybr Challenge</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/89-keybr-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/89-keybr-challenge/</guid>
      <description>My typing skills are horrible, and for quite a few months Ted has been emphasizing the importance of developing this skill.
A healthy bet has emerged between Ted and I. I need to get to an average of 50 wpm faster than him to 100 wpm typing.
My initial average 26.2 wpm (07/28). Current average 34.3 wpm (08/06)
The loser has to prepare a fancy dinner.
I got thisKeybr ProfileKeybr Profile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#0.75 Healthy Habits</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/88-healthyhabits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/88-healthyhabits/</guid>
      <description>Week 32 &amp;amp; 33  Training (Nike Training App, Olie, Running) at least 3 times a week. Gratitude Journal  Weeks 29, 30, 31 - Review My faleo streak of the healthy habits I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to cultivate this past couple of weeks.
MeditationSleep time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#2 Connections</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/connections/</guid>
      <description>Another month, another chapter in the Happiness Project and, August is going to be all about Social Connections.
In less than 10 days we&amp;rsquo;ll be moving to the Northern Hemisphere. And although I&amp;rsquo;m excited about this new life- chapter, I want to stop daydreaming and actually make the most out of these next couple of days.
The quarantine is still pretty strict here in Buenos Aires and that posses some issues with seeing my friends, as some are more comfortable than others violating the general advice of &amp;ldquo;stay at home and see no one&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Full Moon</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/full-moon-ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/full-moon-ba/</guid>
      <description>Three things cannot be long hidden: the Sun, the Moon and Truth
  The Buddha
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 Home and Clutter: Wrap- up</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/homeclutter-warp-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/homeclutter-warp-up/</guid>
      <description>The first month of the Happiness Project is over. I choose Home and Clutter as my first category because we knew we had to move soon. Now we know for a fact we&amp;rsquo;ll be traveling with Frankie and everything in 12 days!
I must admit I did not enjoy it as much as I thought I was going to. Going through every room and deciding what to take, what to give, and what to throw was a great source of anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a beautiful day in this neighborhood - part ii</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/a-beautiful-neighborhood-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/a-beautiful-neighborhood-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>i - meditation studio; ii - yoga studio; iii - le ble; iv - blanca&amp;rsquo;s verduleria; v- a wall</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a beautiful day in this neighborhood</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/a-beautiful-neighborhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/a-beautiful-neighborhood/</guid>
      <description>i - granada; ii - shadow; iii - balcon; iv, v - trains I &amp;amp; II; vi - green bridge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three things about today</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/three-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/three-things/</guid>
      <description>#1 Its official, only 18 days till moving to Philly#2 It was a carrot day cake 🐰
#3 A great book can make you care about people you&amp;rsquo;ll never meet and explore a mind we&amp;rsquo;ll never have.
We all need a Auri perspective to life and the world: an open heart to beauty, a willingness to listen and, the selfishness and diligent care of helping people and things to find their appropiate place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doomsdale</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/domsdale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/domsdale/</guid>
      <description>aka doomsdayThe prospects for human- species annihilation seem to be greater than ever before. Some of these topics are already being debated, without much success, like climate change and global pandemics; but there are others to which the majority of the population seems to be oblivious. AI is one of them. And now to that list of obscure topics that threaten our existence, I&amp;rsquo;ll have to add nuclear war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on repeat (forever)</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/folklore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/folklore/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another day...</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/anotherday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/anotherday/</guid>
      <description>...another Peloton challenge failed,another meditation streak lost. home-made bread, the cause
BEGIN AGAIN
...and a Taylor Swift&#39;s Folklore is coming out tonight...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KonMari - A re-read</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/konmari/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 07:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/konmari/</guid>
      <description>Growing up, the way my parent&amp;rsquo;s house looked was always a source of stress for me. I was never comfortable. Bringing friends was an avoid-at-all-cost-task. Nothing ever seemed to have a place and stuff just pilled everywhere. Although I won&amp;rsquo;t get into too much detail, I now can understand how that happened (but I do struggle to see how it can still be going on).
So, as soon as I moved with Ted I wanted to avoid all the mistakes I felt my parent&amp;rsquo;s made in their own space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Ted &amp; Joe</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/ted-and-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 07:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/ted-and-joe/</guid>
      <description>For the last year or so I&amp;rsquo;ve been witnessing the unfolding of the United States&amp;rsquo; presidential election. NYT articles, debates, Friday&amp;rsquo;s Shields and Brooks analysis on PBS, Bill Maher, Sam Harris, you name it I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to it all. From the, at one point, 25 nominees of the Democratic Party only Biden is standing.
Ted is very happy about this fact. Although it would have never been his (or probably anybody&amp;rsquo;s) first choice, he seriously believes Biden is the one that will defeat Trump in November.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Had to Start Somewhere</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 07:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/day1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco and Twain</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/sfand-twain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/sfand-twain/</guid>
      <description> “The coldest winter I ever spent was a summer in San Francisco.”
   Mark Twain   A year ago</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Discarding - Book</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/the-art-of-discarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/the-art-of-discarding/</guid>
      <description>Like everyone else, I heard about this book after reading Marie Kondo&amp;rsquo;s The Life-Changing Magic of Tidying Up. We are about to move pretty soon and I need motivation and willingness to let things go. This book provided a lot of motivation for discarding, at times even a little bit too much.
Nagisa clearly states our underlying motivations for not getting rid of our possessions and how sooner or later stuff just ends up overflowing not only physical space but our mental space as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#0.5 Healthy habits</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/73-healthy-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/73-healthy-habits/</guid>
      <description>I was planning on doing an entire month for my vitality category, but I changed my mind. These are the chief pillars for a healthy life and I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to implement them throughout the quarantine with varying degrees of success depending on the week.
In order not to get too overwhelmed I will add these important having in pairs every week. I have a small headstart, as my yoga practice is well established already (Ashtanga Primary Series 5 times a week) and, I&amp;rsquo;ve been meditating on and off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Project - Book</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/72-reviewthp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/72-reviewthp/</guid>
      <description>Often learn more from one person’s highly idiosyncratic experiences than I do from sources that detail universal principles or cite up-to-date studies. I find greater value in what specific individuals tell me worked for them than in any other kind of argument—and that’s true even when we seem to have nothing in common.
Gretchen Rubin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Happiness Project&amp;rdquo; is exactly what the title anticipates: a recollection of her journey through finding a greater sense of joy and happiness through small habit changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Prayer</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/70-aprayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/70-aprayer/</guid>
      <description>For a sennight, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to design the blog I wanted. And deep down I know that day is today that website is going to be deployed into the world-wide-web.
This is an orison to the HUGO-Gods. All this work is not to be in vain. A command shall appear before I and addhana will go live.
So please almighty-HUGO, listen to this prayer, and provide the solution to this predicament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 Home &amp; clutter</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/71-homeclutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/71-homeclutter/</guid>
      <description>Moving is an imminent fact, and therefore the &amp;ldquo;home &amp;amp; clutter&amp;rdquo; category seemed a great place to start my happiness project. Moving is not a minor activity, research cites it as the most stressful life event. Nonetheless, we run with an advantage. As we are moving to a completely different country, time zone, and hemisphere, we trully need to declutter and take only the essentials.
Apart from the physical objects, taking care of the emotional aspect is also tectonic because we won&amp;rsquo;t be living in Argentina for the next 4 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned in (Young)-adulthood, updated</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/69-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/69-rules/</guid>
      <description>You do not rise to the level of your goals. You fall to the level of your systems.
  Habits compound, meaning what you do every day matters more than what you do once in a while.
  Never miss the same event/habit twice.
  Don’t judge easily, you never know what the other person is going through.
  Everything comes with time, so take the time and enjoy the journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Project</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/68-thp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/68-thp/</guid>
      <description>Quarantine has been a rediscovery of Dan Harris and his 10% happier project. I’ve attended all his live meditations (while they were running), enrolled in the TPH app, and I’ve been listening to his podcast almost daily. His book (10% happier) was the first audiobook I listened to in the theme of meditation and Buddhism. I was living in Mexico, just recently started dating Ted and I was open to trying new ways to improve my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attachment</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/67-attachment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/67-attachment/</guid>
      <description>Like every Tuesday morning, yesterday I woke up early, kiss Frankie, and after an hour of journaling, I went grocery shopping.
But, unlike every other Tuesday, Blanca’s vegetable store was closed.
This minor setback disrupted my entire shopping experience. I was so upset. In my head, all there was were thoughts about how dare they close without letting me know and how I should probably start looking for a new vegetable place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peloton Challenge</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/66-pelotonchallenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/66-pelotonchallenge/</guid>
      <description>Moving to the States is exciting for several reasons: Christmases are going to be snowy, and Thanksgiving dinners will have turkey again. But most importantly the amazing world of online shopping will be at our feet and God I’m looking forward to it.
With the COVID situation and the unsafeness associated with close contact activities, we decided the first purchase to be a peloton bike. But in order to make things a little bit more fun, we decided to add a small challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnecting</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/65-reconnecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/65-reconnecting/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I (finally) graduated from college. After years of hard work with countless hours with my butt in the chair and my nose between textbooks, I made it over 5 years of intense work, all summarized in a 40-minute presentation.
Many of my close friends gathered to see the whole thing unfold in youtube, and reading their comments and feeling their virtual presence had a nice comforting sensation in a time where the sense of isolation is the new norm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 30th. The next day</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/64-june30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/64-june30/</guid>
      <description>Today I’m feeling pretty much like Jack Konfield’s book tittle
After the ecstasy, the laundryOr like the fish in the final scene of Finding Nemo, looking around wondering
“now what?”
My undergraduate education concluded yesterday (I’m finally a licenciada), and today life’s goes on, with quarantine more strict than ever and lifting the garlands from the floor.
Nonetheless I’ve never felt luckier to be surrounded by so many amazing people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Gentleman in Moscow - book review</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/63-agim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/63-agim/</guid>
      <description>“if a man does not master his circumstances then he is bound to be mastered by them.”
   Count Alexander Ilyich Rostov   ![bingo]/addhana(/63-AGIM.jpg)
Hotel Metropol, Moscow, Russia (circa 1905). Source Wiki Commons
It is hard finding someone that does not recommend ‘A Gentleman in Moscow‘, from my mother-in-law to my boyfriend and Bill Gates, Count Alexander Ilyich Rostov seems to have earned a place in everyone’s heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Through the Window</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/62-mornings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/62-mornings/</guid>
      <description>… Morning visitors ☀️</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bingo!</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/61-bingo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/61-bingo/</guid>
      <description>As part of my (many) quarantine challenges, I started playing Scrabble last week.
I’m not a natural. English is not my mother’s tongue and although I’ve always read a lot it was not until I had to sit for the GRE, and encountered the monstrous Verbal Section, that I made a conscious effort to expand my vocabulary.
The bright side of this whole endeavor is that there’s lots of room for improvement 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Success</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/60-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/60-success/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished the Success course offered by Wharton and all I can say are positive things about it. This course was great. The content in itself might not be mind-blowing (at the end of the day we all know that there’s an inner and outer sphere of success), but the exercises provided by Richard Shell, the instructor were poignant. They kept me thinking in these topics even after the lecture was done, and sparked pages of introspection in my morning journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Last Week Mindset - an analysis</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/59-quarantinemindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/59-quarantinemindset/</guid>
      <description>For someone whose first thought in the morning is setting the intention for a mindful day (however that wants to manifest itself that day) I found it fascinating how my mind has been residing in imagination this past couple of weeks. My last post is living proof of that. This quarantine, and the incapacity for action I feel due to the confinement has got me into self-centered loops of thoughts with a pretty obvious theme: wanting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Week Mindset</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/58-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/58-mindset/</guid>
      <description>I wish I there was no COVID; I wish there was no quarantine; I wish it hasn’t been extended two more weeks; I wish I had bought a sewing machine a couple of months ago; I wish I could have all the right colors of yarn to crochet all the amigurumi in Pica Pau’s latest book; I wish I would have started learning to weave, now I do not have a loom; I wish I was in Mexico; I wish I was in Malta; I wish I was in the Philippines or maybe Bali; I wish we were already in Philly; I wish I could have been with my grandad in his birthday (May 16th); I wish I can be with my brother in his birthday (June 19th), at least I was able to be with Ted in his birthday (April 29th); I’ll probably be able to be with my mum in her 50th birthday, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinnamon Rolls</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/57-cr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/57-cr/</guid>
      <description>Today was the first time in 66 days of quarantine that I cooked something other than a salad (needless to say I think is the first time I attempted to use the oven in 2 years since we moved here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandiculations</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/56-pandiculations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/56-pandiculations/</guid>
      <description>then and now 2017 – No formal yoga practice and obviously not scared of touching the floor in a random place in Mexico
  2020 – Ashtanga Quarantine practice in my dark room
  pandiculation (noun) – a stretching and stiffening especially of the trunk and extremities
   Merriam Webster   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30&#43; days</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/55-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/55-streak/</guid>
      <description>Postcards from the cushion</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Earth in a Poem</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/54-teiap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/54-teiap/</guid>
      <description>We say that you cannot divert the river from the riverbed. We say that everything is moving, and we are part of this motion, that the soil is moving, that the water is moving. We say that the earth draws water to her from the clouds. We say the rainfall parts on each side of the mountain like the parting of our hair, and that the shape of the mountain tells where the water has passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Anger</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/53-onanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/53-onanger/</guid>
      <description>For my granddad. Happy 86th Birthday A couple of valuable lessons became evident after my grandma bashed to me over the phone the other day:
  #1. Her anger and mistreatment reflect nothing about me but everything about her. And more importantly, it is impersonal.
  #2. Non-engagement in violent speech is the best tool to dismembering the anger you are receiving from the other side. When two people are acting mean to each other it’s a fight but, when only one of the parties is involved it’s just a crazy person yelling over a phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streak</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/52-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/52-streak/</guid>
      <description>… and 5 thoughts on intermittent fasting (IF) I.F. really help with my morning-crush. When I’m not fasting, after breakfast I experience low energy where I could think of is crawling back to bed. IF has really helped me with the morning crush, allowing me to be more productive and have a more energy-stable day Because I break my IF with a big healthy lunch, I’m less incline to take little snacks through out the day (although yesterday after a toxic conversation with my grandmother I ate half a carrot budín).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Lessons</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/51-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/51-lessons/</guid>
      <description>1. When ordering ice cream it is important to only order fruit flavors or cream flavors. The mixture of the two is considered heresy. 2. Always read a book from cover to cover. You do not know what wisdom gems might be awaiting at the very end. 3. When your motives are unclear, is always better not to act. They might became apparent when emotions have settled. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fasting</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/50-fasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/50-fasting/</guid>
      <description>Since Sunday I’ve began intermittent fasting.
I’m using a great app, Zero, to track the 16:8 cycle.
Chores have been distributed the following way during the past couple of weeks of quarantine:
Mica – lunch Ted – dinner Since Monday Ted asks me (anxiously) around noon when I’m going to take care of lunch. Because of the 16 hour fast window, lately it has been around 2 o’clock, failing to realize this fundamental truth about our new lunch schedule:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling quesosa</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/49-quesosa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/49-quesosa/</guid>
      <description>In the past months I went from being the happy state of singletown to the happy silly state of ‘Hey! This is my boyfriend. Have I told you he is the most amazing person in the world (yes, probably like a thousand times)
  Being in love is like that – silly, inexplicable
  It simply just happens
  Sometimes we do look for it a little bit under some random rocks we encounter in our journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎓🎓 The Science of Well-Being</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/48-tswb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/48-tswb/</guid>
      <description>This quarantine was all about happiness, self- improvement, and habits. Yesterday I officially completed Yale’s most popular class ever and my 2nd (actually 3rd) Coursera course during the COVID19 lock-down, The Science of Well-Being.
I enjoyed the course so much, that I enrolled in the UPenn Foundations of Positive Psychology Specialization and already audited Part I. It is a long course lasting a total of 10 weeks, I manage to complete it in 5 weeks by bingeing the first week through all the lectures and leaving the last 4 weeks for the Final Reweirement Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎓 Buddhism and Modern Psychology</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/47-moocbuddhism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/47-moocbuddhism/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely loved this course. Robert Wright is a funny guy and his way of delivering hard concepts is pretty good. The course tries to bring together the Naturalistic (sometimes called Secular) notions of Buddhism under the scientific framework of Modern Evolutionary Psychology.
My grade was 95%
I&amp;rsquo;m obssesed with my newly found bitmojis</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doppelgänger</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/46-doppelganger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/46-doppelganger/</guid>
      <description>Recent studies have shown that dogs adopt some personality traits of their owner.
Every morning after watching my little Buddha contemplate the Truth of impermanence from his favorite spot in the balcony, I wonder if the opposite can be true.
April 21st, Colegiales, Argentina</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anicca</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/45-annica/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/45-annica/</guid>
      <description>the state or fact of lasting for only a limited period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/44-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/44-fall/</guid>
      <description>Leaves budgeto the autumn zephyr pervading the sepia sky with dances and swirls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papañca</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/43-papanca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/43-papanca/</guid>
      <description>Papañca is the Pali term used to describe the tendency of the mind to spread out from and elaborate upon any sense object that arises in experience, smothering it with wave after wave of mental elaboration, most of which is illusory, repetitive, and even obsessive, which effectively blocks any sort of mental calm or clarity of mind.
   Lion’s Roar Website
 This was my intended name for the blog, I end up choosing Addhana</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micaism</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/42-micaism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/42-micaism/</guid>
      <description>micaism  /ˈmʌɪkəˈɪz(ə)m/
  noun
 a deep understanding of the difference between the relative and absolute levels of Truth.   like in &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;hellip; but no&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multitasking</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/41-multitasking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/41-multitasking/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered my boyfriend can actually do two things at the same time.
Which ones, I rather not say</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sesīr kipi</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/39-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/39-back/</guid>
      <description>Aerēbassiks dāeremaa aōhon vȳs
Aerēbassiks kisikaa gīs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/39-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/39-back/</guid>
      <description>I’m back! After a month almost of no updates, I decided (my followers, Ted, asked for it) to come back to blogging. Being in Argentina, these past weeks have been crazy with family meeting, friends to see, coffee shops to explore, studying to do, old photo albums to flip through, books to read, pinky foot toe to heal, habits to break. It also included my very first Thanksgiving celebration.
Holidays + Mexico Round 2 are coming soon and I could be more excited about what the future has to hold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Registrado</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/38-caferegistrado/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/38-caferegistrado/</guid>
      <description>✔️ best scrambled eggs in Buenos Aires</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mum</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/37-mum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/37-mum/</guid>
      <description>Best day in a long time. Being away so long I miss days like today… Just spending the whole day with my mum, doing nothing and everything at the same time. Drinking mates, catching up, laughing, talking and gossiping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/36-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/36-stuff/</guid>
      <description>So much stuff! Coming back home and all I do is pile up all the stuff I own. Piles of books, piles of pages, piles of photographs, piles of bags, piles of shoes, t- shirts, skirts, piles of sh*t everywhere.
Need to regain control of my space starting now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bs As List</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/35-bsaslist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/35-bsaslist/</guid>
      <description>Since Ted told me he was coming to Buenos Aires I made a list of my favorite spots in my neighborhood, La Lucila. Almost a week into our Buenos Aires adventure (or how we call it, Chapter 6) this is how out list is going
Best fabrica de pasta – La Imperial. Glorious ravioli and fetuccini we (Ted) cooked to my family
Best medialunas – La de Vicente López. Service was okay, but oh my God those buttered medialunas are always the best</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raqnon</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/34-raqnon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/34-raqnon/</guid>
      <description> Your task is not seek for love, but merely to seek and find all the barriers within yourself that you have built against it
  Rumi – ‘Why Buddhism is true’
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13 hour flight and counting</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/33-13hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/33-13hour/</guid>
      <description>The Andes
Last stop Lima. Final destination Buenos Aires. Estimation time 5.30 hours</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunrise &amp; coffee</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/32-sunrisecoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/32-sunrisecoffee/</guid>
      <description> The meaning of life is just to be alive. It is so plain and so obvious and so simple. And yet, everybody rushes around in a great panic as if it were necessary to achieve something beyond themselves
  Alan Watts
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Day</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/31-lastday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/31-lastday/</guid>
      <description>Last day in this wonderful place with the most beautiful skies in the world.
Going back home 🇦🇷</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ēlie 100</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/30-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/30-100/</guid>
      <description>Gār tubissa istin, se gār tolī mirre jaelagon kostan.
Avy jorrāelan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photographs</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/29-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/29-photos/</guid>
      <description>The organization of my digital life just took a new level, I just started organizing my Google Photos website. I was always a little obsessed with photographs and not wanting to lose them so, it hurts to know all those pictures I lost from my teen years when cellphones and digital cameras just started, backups where a tedious thing and only god knows where those pictures are but I have a decent collection starting 2009 and from my early childhood (thanks mum).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Mile</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/28-8mile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/28-8mile/</guid>
      <description>8 mile
Next stop Playa and meditation retreat for 7 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind Giants</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/27-windgiants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/27-windgiants/</guid>
      <description>La ventura va guiando nuestras cosas mejor de lo que acertáramos a desear; porque ves allí, amigo Sancho Panza, donde se descubren treinta o pocos más desaforados gigantes, con quien pienso hacer batalla y quitarles a todos las vidas, con cuyos despojos comenzaremos a enriquecer, que esta es buena guerra, y es gran servicio de Dios quitar tan mala simiente de sobre la faz de la tierra
  Don Quijote de la Mancha – capítulo VIII</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/27-windgiants.md/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/27-windgiants.md/</guid>
      <description>Day 100 – The other side is Canada</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bē sōvegon – vāedar</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/25-hp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/25-hp/</guid>
      <description>Harry, hen ziry ēlie kipagon zaldrīzes ābrarra
Skorī nuke ñuhon zaldrīzi
Rȳ ēbrio sōven
Zirtys jelmio vujīn
Lōz sambār iksan
Qēlossa ñuhoso siki
Paerī, vīzos zȳhos ōñoso yno jehikā</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Image</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/24-mentalimage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/24-mentalimage/</guid>
      <description>Time in Playa del Carmen is coming to an end. The next 10 days are fully occupied with traveling and DIY meditation retreats, so we decided take a day off and give one last visit technology-free visit of the year to our place in the world (La Zebra) .
My inner goal was to try to stay mindful all day (or at least most of it). So here are some mental highlights of the day:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E.T. phone home</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/23-et/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/23-et/</guid>
      <description>November 4th was my dad’s birthday so I called home to be present being far away. Truth is while I’m traveling I hardly ever call home, I don’t like it, too much me- focus, but I try to make exceptions during special occasion like this one. Half my family is at the country house, the other is getting there the next day for the big asado.
I haven’t even send him a text message as we were on our technology- free day off, out all day in Tulum; so I decided to do a ‘surprise’ WhatsApp video call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[fil-a-vuh-ri]</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/22-philavery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/22-philavery/</guid>
      <description>Philavery = an idiosyncratic collection of uncommon and pleasing words.
 I encountered Foyle’s Philavery, a little flowered covered book with red spines, while I was working at a bookshop a couple of years ago. The term stick with me so much that I used it as the tittle of my lists of new words in every journal since then. Here’s a small recollection of my last added words:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 requests</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/21-2requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/21-2requests/</guid>
      <description>Me
‘I’m going for a walk. You will probably be in cloud nine when I come back, so please: 1. Leave me at least a third of the bed, 2. Don’t steal my pillow’
That’s me failing at the most basic requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🌕 - moonlight</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/20-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/20-moon/</guid>
      <description>Full Moon, Playa del Carmen
Pictures are not as good enough as a memory but they are the closest thing we got.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ñuhon geltītsos amāzigon jaelagan</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/19-iwmhb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/19-iwmhb/</guid>
      <description>page of ‘I Want my Hat back’ but Jon Klessen
After a week in which I experienced every flavor of thought available to mankind (anxiousness, sadness, hopelessness, happiness and anxiety again), I found the best way for coping with this fluctuating state of mind… simply re- read your favorite children’s book. The simplicity of it all gives you a great perspective of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dia de los Muetos</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/18-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/18-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Holidays like Día de los muertos (Halloween) make me feel an outsider of my own species.
Is not that I don’t like going out, but I just don’t feel such a strong feeling to connect with the masses in these kind of commercial holidays, probably just using them as an excuse to either eat a bunch of sugar in the form of hard candy or get dressed in an unusual, weird ‘likely to be regretted a couple of years from now’ way, and get drunk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bē yno</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/17-beyno/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/17-beyno/</guid>
      <description>Micaerys hen Ninnīrio Letrot brōziks. Brōzio tubis lantēpsa tōma iksan. Valyrio muño ēngos ñuhys issa daor yn gūrēñan. Ao Qeptenkys Ēngos temptys iksan. Lanta jaohossa se lanta kēla eman, pōntes Nonnōkerys, Ummērys, Oreys, Torāys brōzan. Pikīnnon se gureñon yne raqiros issi. Muña blog ōtapnoso tubī bardun.
I am called Micaela of House Ninni. I am 25 name days. Valyrian is not my mother tongue but I’m learning. I am a common tongue teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>battles</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/16-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/16-battles/</guid>
      <description>The Morning and I
A lesson I learned a long time ago:
Not all battles are worth fighting for. The hard part is choosing the correct ones
Like my hair this morning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decisions</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/15-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/15-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Life is a huge decision making process, everything revolving our lives was a decision taken at some point.
A big question is, what degree of freedom we have in our decisions? A few days ago this question was posted on our coffee break, and some people smarter than me stated there is no such thing as freewill, and that in this sense our brain does not really evaluate options, but the decision is already made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Togetherness</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/14-togetherness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/14-togetherness/</guid>
      <description>The Moment
The memory of the first time I thought ‘There might be something here’ is still crystal clear in my mind. It was an afternoon, after our half- failed Appalachian hiking, we both were reading minding our own business but being there for each other. I was with my Kindle with ‘Eating animals‘, he was with his hardcover of ‘Why Buddhism is True‘. I was laying on the couch, he was sitting on the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Them Cry</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/13-letthemcry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/13-letthemcry/</guid>
      <description>A perfect image of my mind today
Today’s morning was one of THOSE morning. You know, those type of mornings (sometimes it can last the whole day) where no matter what you are doing, you could always be doing something better.
When I was journaling, I wanted to study High Valyrian
When I was learning High Valyrian, I wanted to be at the 9am yoga class
When I decided I was not going to yoga in the morning but rather leave it for the afternoon, I wanted a coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October, 28th - a memoir</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/12-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/12-today/</guid>
      <description>Downward facing dog?
Today was a good days in many ways. I gave my first Spanish lesson, I’m seeing some extraordinary progress in my English student, tried the recipe for avocado dressing (without the basil), have some beautiful orange flowers in my coffee table, ate an amazing salad for lunch, continue improving on my High Valyrian, meditated (or I’m going to in a couple of minutes), had a breakfast- type dinner, cleaned the house (that’s looking so nice), organized the kitchen shelf, drank mate, tried a piece of plum tart from the bakery shop around the corner, wrote my dad his birthday card, mum sent me pictures of my granddad’s french play, talked to friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Word Post</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/11-lazebra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/11-lazebra/</guid>
      <description>La Zebra, Tulum</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 days of High Valyrian</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/10-10daysofhv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/10-10daysofhv/</guid>
      <description>I’m a nerd.
There’s no news on the statement made above, I know it, you know it, we all know it, and fantasy books bring the most nerdy part of my personality. I read Harry Potter so many times in my life that I already lost count of them and the past couple of years my time has been divided between The Kingkiller Chronicles by Patrick Ruthfuss and, of course, the amazing A Song of Ice and Fire Series by GRR Martin (yes, I read the books before the series came out; no, I did not like the last season but every Sunday at 9pm I was religiously sat in front of the TV no matter what part of the world I was anyway).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bucket Full of Flowers</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/9-abucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/9-abucket/</guid>
      <description>‘On Sundays the office is closed’ or so my boyfriend thought one of the first weekends we were at Playa del Carmen. I had woken up early to go to the market to buy groceries and such, when I saw a small stand were they were selling flowers; huge beautiful yellow, white, orange flowers. I thought flowers would make home a much cheerful place to work so I decided to buy flowers for my boyfriend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Week of Blogging</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/8-aweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/8-aweek/</guid>
      <description>My first week of blogging is over and here are 7 highlights:
  According to people I write better than I talk (so imagine how I talk)
  It liberates your mind from random thoughts that keep appearing on a daily basis, it’s all about uncluttering
  Creating habits is easier when you are doing it with somebody else
  You can create a great unintended debate at dinnertime</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>past</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/7-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/7-past/</guid>
      <description>It’s amazing how the past lingers with us, even when we try to push it away. How things that we worked so much on, in many cases convincing ourselves that we had made peace with them, can find us in the most unthought places triggered by the most unusual things, like a phrase on a blog post.
I think this is true because we cannot really escape from those deterrent moments that made us who we are, no matter how much emotional- baggage they still carry with them; and that is due to those moments, that we are where we are right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Enthusiast</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/6-naturalenthusiast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/6-naturalenthusiast/</guid>
      <description>I’m a natural enthusiast.
Wait! you never heard this before? Good, me neither and is because I just made this up. This is no psychological diagnose or anything of that sort is just the way I’ve always been and that I think, right now, is the main reason of a great distress in my head.
I think I’m going through a quarter-of-a-century kinda crisis. I wake up every morning not knowing what I am going to do or where I’m heading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Hunt</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/5-jobhunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/5-jobhunt/</guid>
      <description>After a couple months in low- season Playa del Carmen I came to the realization that life is harder than it seems. I never considered myself lucky with my past jobs (always grateful, never lucky) but after a month of trying to get a decent paycheck in Mexico I started believing I was. Being a full time student of an (yet) unfinished major for most of my adult life, working was never a top priority for me, so my past jobs were jobs that I performed to have some kind of personal income or to pay for that year’s vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me too</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/4-metoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/4-metoo/</guid>
      <description>Every night when I go to bed I kiss my boyfriend goodnight, look at him in the eyes and tell him ‘I love you, baby’, After what follows complete silence.
It’s been a little bit less than 2 months since I made that first statement driving through Virginia the day I decided I was going to loose my flight ticket to explore the perks of living in Mexico with someone I met on a plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>123</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/3-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/3-123/</guid>
      <description>It was a beautiful late summer afternoon, we were sitting on the porch, drinking mate drinking in Harrisonburg, the day we decided to live with less stuff. “We should be able to name everything we own” and so we settle on the quest to own 123 things. And although we don’t really keep track of the amount of things do think we been living with less things we normally did and made smarter shopping decisions when we had to make a 2-month apartment into a home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why am I doing this?</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/2-whyamidoingthis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/2-whyamidoingthis/</guid>
      <description>Why am I writing a post a day? I think the best definition I could find was:
“I want to write down my thoughts somewhere where I won’t be able to loose them or throw them away”
ecause that’s our tendency as Homo sapiens, to project certain perfection or vision of ourselves and see if we can deceive ourselves along the way too.
In that way when a writing is not what we expect, we discard it; when a feeling that is not ‘positive’ or align with the ideal ‘me’ we tend to forget and pretend it was never there in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post by post</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/1-postbypost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/1-postbypost/</guid>
      <description>“Writing a novel is like driving a car at night. You can only see as far as your headlights go, but you can make the whole trip that way”
E. L. Doctorow – Bird by Bird by Anne Lamott
And I kinda feel this is how my whole journey will go,
step by step, post by post
or as Anne’s father liked to say bird by bird
as I have never done anything like this before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>material properties</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/materialp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/materialp/</guid>
      <description>Material Properties Room Temperature Density Room Temperature Stiffness Room Temperature Strengths Room Temperature Resistance to Fracture Room Temperature Electrical Conductivity Modulus of Elasticity (Stiffness) vs. Density </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>