<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lessons on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/tags/lessons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lessons on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/tags/lessons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules of Adulthood, updated</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/69-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/69-rules/</guid>
      <description>You do not rise to the level of your goals. You fall to the level of your systems.
  Habits compound, meaning what you do every day matters more than what you do once in a while.
  Never miss the same event/habit twice.
  Don’t judge easily, you never know what the other person is going through.
  Everything comes with time, so take the time and enjoy the journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 30th. The next day</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/64-june30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/64-june30/</guid>
      <description>Today I’m feeling pretty much like Jack Konfield’s book tittle
After the ecstasy, the laundry Or like the fish in the final scene of Finding Nemo, looking around wondering
“now what?”
My undergraduate education concluded yesterday (I’m finally a licenciada), and today life’s goes on, with quarantine more strict than ever and lifting the garlands from the floor.
Nonetheless I’ve never felt luckier to be surrounded by so many amazing people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Earth in a Poem</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/54-teiap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/54-teiap/</guid>
      <description>We say that you cannot divert the river from the riverbed. We say that everything is moving, and we are part of this motion, that the soil is moving, that the water is moving. We say that the earth draws water to her from the clouds. We say the rainfall parts on each side of the mountain like the parting of our hair, and that the shape of the mountain tells where the water has passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Anger</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/53-onanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/53-onanger/</guid>
      <description>For my granddad. Happy 86th Birthday A couple of valuable lessons became evident after my grandma bashed to me over the phone the other day:
  #1. Her anger and mistreatment reflect nothing about me but everything about her. And more importantly, it is impersonal.
  #2. Non-engagement in violent speech is the best tool to dismembering the anger you are receiving from the other side. When two people are acting mean to each other it’s a fight but, when only one of the parties is involved it’s just a crazy person yelling over a phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streak</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/52-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/52-streak/</guid>
      <description>… and 5 thoughts on intermittent fasting (IF)  I.F. really help with my morning-crush. When I’m not fasting, after breakfast I experience low energy where I could think of is crawling back to bed. IF has really helped me with the morning crush, allowing me to be more productive and have a more energy-stable day Because I break my IF with a big healthy lunch, I’m less incline to take little snacks through out the day (although yesterday after a toxic conversation with my grandmother I ate half a carrot budín).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Lessons</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/51-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/51-lessons/</guid>
      <description>1. When ordering ice cream it is important to only order fruit flavors or cream flavors. The mixture of the two is considered heresy. 2. Always read a book from cover to cover. You do not know what wisdom gems might be awaiting at the very end 3. When your motives are unclear, is always better not to act. They might became apparent when emotions have settled. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fasting</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/50-fasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/50-fasting/</guid>
      <description>Since Sunday I’ve began intermittent fasting.
I’m using a great app, Zero, to track the 16:8 cycle.
Chores have been distributed the following way during the past couple of weeks of quarantine:
Mica – lunch Ted – dinner Since Monday Ted asks me (anxiously) around noon when I’m going to take care of lunch. Because of the 16 hour fast window, lately it has been around 2 o’clock, failing to realize this fundamental truth about our new lunch schedule:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>battles</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/16-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/16-battles/</guid>
      <description>The Morning and I
A lesson I learned a long time ago:
Not all battles are worth fighting for. The hard part is choosing the correct ones
Like my hair this morning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why am I doing this?</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/2-whyamidoingthis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/2-whyamidoingthis/</guid>
      <description>Why am I writing a post a day? I think the best definition I could find was:
“I want to write down my thoughts somewhere where I won’t be able to loose them or throw them away”
ecause that’s our tendency as Homo sapiens, to project certain perfection or vision of ourselves and see if we can deceive ourselves along the way too.
In that way when a writing is not what we expect, we discard it; when a feeling that is not ‘positive’ or align with the ideal ‘me’ we tend to forget and pretend it was never there in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post by post</title>
      <link>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/1-postbypost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mica-92.github.io/addhana/blog/1-postbypost/</guid>
      <description>“Writing a novel is like driving a car at night. You can only see as far as your headlights go, but you can make the whole trip that way”
E. L. Doctorow – Bird by Bird by Anne Lamott
And I kinda feel this is how my whole journey will go,
step by step, post by post
or as Anne’s father liked to say bird by bird
as I have never done anything like this before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>