<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>quarantine on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/quarantine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in quarantine on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/quarantine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Project</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/68-thp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/68-thp/</guid>
      <description>Quarantine has been a rediscovery of Dan Harris and his 10% happier project. I’ve attended all his live meditations (while they were running), enrolled in the TPH app, and I’ve been listening to his podcast almost daily. His book (10% happier) was the first audiobook I listened to in the theme of meditation and Buddhism. I was living in Mexico, just recently started dating Ted and I was open to trying new ways to improve my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attachment</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/67-attachment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/67-attachment/</guid>
      <description>Like every Tuesday morning, yesterday I woke up early, kiss Frankie, and after an hour of journaling, I went grocery shopping.
But, unlike every other Tuesday, Blanca’s vegetable store was closed.
This minor setback disrupted my entire shopping experience. I was so upset. In my head, all there was were thoughts about how dare they close without letting me know and how I should probably start looking for a new vegetable place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peloton Challenge</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/66-pelotonchallenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/66-pelotonchallenge/</guid>
      <description>Moving to the States is exciting for several reasons: Christmases are going to be snowy, and Thanksgiving dinners will have turkey again. But most importantly the amazing world of online shopping will be at our feet and God I’m looking forward to it.
With the COVID situation and the unsafeness associated with close contact activities, we decided the first purchase to be a peloton bike. But in order to make things a little bit more fun, we decided to add a small challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>