<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>experience on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in experience on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with 💚 by Mica, 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>past</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/7-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/7-past/</guid>
      <description>It’s amazing how the past lingers with us, even when we try to push it away. How things that we worked so much on, in many cases convincing ourselves that we had made peace with them, can find us in the most unthought places triggered by the most unusual things, like a phrase on a blog post.
I think this is true because we cannot really escape from those deterrent moments that made us who we are, no matter how much emotional- baggage they still carry with them; and that is due to those moments, that we are where we are right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Enthusiast</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/6-naturalenthusiast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/6-naturalenthusiast/</guid>
      <description>I’m a natural enthusiast.
Wait! you never heard this before? Good, me neither and is because I just made this up. This is no psychological diagnose or anything of that sort is just the way I’ve always been and that I think, right now, is the main reason of a great distress in my head.
I think I’m going through a quarter-of-a-century kinda crisis. I wake up every morning not knowing what I am going to do or where I’m heading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Hunt</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/5-jobhunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/5-jobhunt/</guid>
      <description>After a couple months in low- season Playa del Carmen I came to the realization that life is harder than it seems. I never considered myself lucky with my past jobs (always grateful, never lucky) but after a month of trying to get a decent paycheck in Mexico I started believing I was. Being a full time student of an (yet) unfinished major for most of my adult life, working was never a top priority for me, so my past jobs were jobs that I performed to have some kind of personal income or to pay for that year’s vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>