<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>happiness-project on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/happiness-project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in happiness-project on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with 💚 by Mica, 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/happiness-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#0.75 Healthy Habits</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/88-healthyhabits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/88-healthyhabits/</guid>
      <description>Week 32 &amp;amp; 33  Training (Nike Training App, Olie, Running) at least 3 times a week. Gratitude Journal  Weeks 29, 30, 31 - Review My faleo streak of the healthy habits I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to cultivate this past couple of weeks.
MeditationSleep time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#2 Connections</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/connections/</guid>
      <description>Another month, another chapter in the Happiness Project and, August is going to be all about Social Connections.
In less than 10 days we&amp;rsquo;ll be moving to the Northern Hemisphere. And although I&amp;rsquo;m excited about this new life- chapter, I want to stop daydreaming and actually make the most out of these next couple of days.
The quarantine is still pretty strict here in Buenos Aires and that posses some issues with seeing my friends, as some are more comfortable than others violating the general advice of &amp;ldquo;stay at home and see no one&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 Home and Clutter: Wrap- up</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/homeclutter-warp-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/homeclutter-warp-up/</guid>
      <description>The first month of the Happiness Project is over. I choose Home and Clutter as my first category because we knew we had to move soon. Now we know for a fact we&amp;rsquo;ll be traveling with Frankie and everything in 12 days!
I must admit I did not enjoy it as much as I thought I was going to. Going through every room and deciding what to take, what to give, and what to throw was a great source of anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KonMari - A re-read</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/konmari/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 07:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/konmari/</guid>
      <description>Growing up, the way my parent&amp;rsquo;s house looked was always a source of stress for me. I was never comfortable. Bringing friends was an avoid-at-all-cost-task. Nothing ever seemed to have a place and stuff just pilled everywhere. Although I won&amp;rsquo;t get into too much detail, I now can understand how that happened (but I do struggle to see how it can still be going on).
So, as soon as I moved with Ted I wanted to avoid all the mistakes I felt my parent&amp;rsquo;s made in their own space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Discarding - Book</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/the-art-of-discarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/the-art-of-discarding/</guid>
      <description>Like everyone else, I heard about this book after reading Marie Kondo&amp;rsquo;s The Life-Changing Magic of Tidying Up. We are about to move pretty soon and I need motivation and willingness to let things go. This book provided a lot of motivation for discarding, at times even a little bit too much.
Nagisa clearly states our underlying motivations for not getting rid of our possessions and how sooner or later stuff just ends up overflowing not only physical space but our mental space as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#0.5 Healthy habits</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/73-healthy-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/73-healthy-habits/</guid>
      <description>I was planning on doing an entire month for my vitality category, but I changed my mind. These are the chief pillars for a healthy life and I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to implement them throughout the quarantine with varying degrees of success depending on the week.
In order not to get too overwhelmed I will add these important having in pairs every week. I have a small headstart, as my yoga practice is well established already (Ashtanga Primary Series 5 times a week) and, I&amp;rsquo;ve been meditating on and off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Project - Book</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/72-reviewthp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/72-reviewthp/</guid>
      <description>Often learn more from one person’s highly idiosyncratic experiences than I do from sources that detail universal principles or cite up-to-date studies. I find greater value in what specific individuals tell me worked for them than in any other kind of argument—and that’s true even when we seem to have nothing in common.
Gretchen Rubin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Happiness Project&amp;rdquo; is exactly what the title anticipates: a recollection of her journey through finding a greater sense of joy and happiness through small habit changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 Home &amp; clutter</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/71-homeclutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/71-homeclutter/</guid>
      <description>Moving is an imminent fact, and therefore the &amp;ldquo;home &amp;amp; clutter&amp;rdquo; category seemed a great place to start my happiness project. Moving is not a minor activity, research cites it as the most stressful life event. Nonetheless, we run with an advantage. As we are moving to a completely different country, time zone, and hemisphere, we trully need to declutter and take only the essentials.
Apart from the physical objects, taking care of the emotional aspect is also tectonic because we won&amp;rsquo;t be living in Argentina for the next 4 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned in (Young)-adulthood, updated</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/69-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/69-rules/</guid>
      <description>You do not rise to the level of your goals. You fall to the level of your systems.
  Habits compound, meaning what you do every day matters more than what you do once in a while.
  Never miss the same event/habit twice.
  Don’t judge easily, you never know what the other person is going through.
  Everything comes with time, so take the time and enjoy the journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Project</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/68-thp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/68-thp/</guid>
      <description>Quarantine has been a rediscovery of Dan Harris and his 10% happier project. I’ve attended all his live meditations (while they were running), enrolled in the TPH app, and I’ve been listening to his podcast almost daily. His book (10% happier) was the first audiobook I listened to in the theme of meditation and Buddhism. I was living in Mexico, just recently started dating Ted and I was open to trying new ways to improve my life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>