<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phialdelphia on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/phialdelphia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Phialdelphia on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with 💚 by Mica, 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:10:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/phialdelphia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>academic website deployed and running</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/111-personalwebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:10:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/111-personalwebsite/</guid>
      <description>One final resolution I sat for 2020 was to upgrade my professional information. For this, I create a Research Gate and LinkedIn account, make available to the world my undergrad-senior thesis, and update my CV with a profile section (+ try to make it bulkier with some minor recent accomplishments).
Little would I&amp;rsquo;ve known that my résumé&amp;rsquo;s final version will evolve to be a personal website. The thoughts behind this crazy endeavor lay in the fact that developing my professional website will give lots of room to explore and share my research and other professional interest with everyone while being detached from the social media standards and recipes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>open fronts</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/110-openfronts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:10:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/110-openfronts/</guid>
      <description>A list of side projects I started at some point and hope to continue in 2021  Personal Blog (addhana.com) or the website where you are reading this post: I won&amp;rsquo;t try to commit a blog a day because I don&amp;rsquo;t trust myself with that responsibility; I&amp;rsquo;ll simply try to keep it active and try to switch from guilt to fun. I&amp;rsquo;ve written quite a few posts in the last couple of weeks that I never pushed because I felt they were incomplete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>evermore</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/109-evermore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/109-evermore/</guid>
      <description>after writing my senior thesis under the influence of Lover.
living my first Penn semester with folklore on repeat (forever).
crying with the long pond sessions
evermore is the best way to share my return home. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>