<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>favorites on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/favorites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in favorites on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/favorites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Prayer</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/70-aprayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/70-aprayer/</guid>
      <description>For a sennight, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to design the blog I wanted. And deep down I know that day is today that website is going to be deployed into the world-wide-web.
This is an orison to the HUGO-Gods. All this work is not to be in vain. A command shall appear before I and addhana will go live.
So please almighty-HUGO, listen to this prayer, and provide the solution to this predicament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned in (Young)-adulthood, updated</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/69-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/69-rules/</guid>
      <description>You do not rise to the level of your goals. You fall to the level of your systems.
  Habits compound, meaning what you do every day matters more than what you do once in a while.
  Never miss the same event/habit twice.
  Don’t judge easily, you never know what the other person is going through.
  Everything comes with time, so take the time and enjoy the journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 30th. The next day</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/64-june30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/64-june30/</guid>
      <description>Today I’m feeling pretty much like Jack Konfield’s book tittle
After the ecstasy, the laundry Or like the fish in the final scene of Finding Nemo, looking around wondering
“now what?”
My undergraduate education concluded yesterday (I’m finally a licenciada), and today life’s goes on, with quarantine more strict than ever and lifting the garlands from the floor.
Nonetheless I’ve never felt luckier to be surrounded by so many amazing people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Anger</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/53-onanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/53-onanger/</guid>
      <description>For my granddad. Happy 86th Birthday A couple of valuable lessons became evident after my grandma bashed to me over the phone the other day:
  #1. Her anger and mistreatment reflect nothing about me but everything about her. And more importantly, it is impersonal.
  #2. Non-engagement in violent speech is the best tool to dismembering the anger you are receiving from the other side. When two people are acting mean to each other it’s a fight but, when only one of the parties is involved it’s just a crazy person yelling over a phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Lessons</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/51-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/51-lessons/</guid>
      <description>1. When ordering ice cream it is important to only order fruit flavors or cream flavors. The mixture of the two is considered heresy. 2. Always read a book from cover to cover. You do not know what wisdom gems might be awaiting at the very end 3. When your motives are unclear, is always better not to act. They might became apparent when emotions have settled. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fasting</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/50-fasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/50-fasting/</guid>
      <description>Since Sunday I’ve began intermittent fasting.
I’m using a great app, Zero, to track the 16:8 cycle.
Chores have been distributed the following way during the past couple of weeks of quarantine:
Mica – lunch Ted – dinner Since Monday Ted asks me (anxiously) around noon when I’m going to take care of lunch. Because of the 16 hour fast window, lately it has been around 2 o’clock, failing to realize this fundamental truth about our new lunch schedule:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multitasking</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/41-multitasking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/41-multitasking/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered my boyfriend can actually do two things at the same time.
Which ones, I rather not say</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October, 28th - a memoir</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/12-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/12-today/</guid>
      <description>Downward facing dog?
Today was a good days in many ways. I gave my first Spanish lesson, I’m seeing some extraordinary progress in my English student, tried the recipe for avocado dressing (without the basil), have some beautiful orange flowers in my coffee table, ate an amazing salad for lunch, continue improving on my High Valyrian, meditated (or I’m going to in a couple of minutes), had a breakfast- type dinner, cleaned the house (that’s looking so nice), organized the kitchen shelf, drank mate, tried a piece of plum tart from the bakery shop around the corner, wrote my dad his birthday card, mum sent me pictures of my granddad’s french play, talked to friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bucket Full of Flowers</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/9-abucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/9-abucket/</guid>
      <description>‘On Sundays the office is closed’ or so my boyfriend thought one of the first weekends we were at Playa del Carmen. I had woken up early to go to the market to buy groceries and such, when I saw a small stand were they were selling flowers; huge beautiful yellow, white, orange flowers. I thought flowers would make home a much cheerful place to work so I decided to buy flowers for my boyfriend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me too</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/4-metoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/4-metoo/</guid>
      <description>Every night when I go to bed I kiss my boyfriend goodnight, look at him in the eyes and tell him ‘I love you, baby’, After what follows complete silence.
It’s been a little bit less than 2 months since I made that first statement driving through Virginia the day I decided I was going to loose my flight ticket to explore the perks of living in Mexico with someone I met on a plane.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>