<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>buddhism on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addahna.com/tags/buddhism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in buddhism on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addahna.com/tags/buddhism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Attachment</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/67-attachment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/67-attachment/</guid>
      <description>Like every Tuesday morning, yesterday I woke up early, kiss Frankie, and after an hour of journaling, I went grocery shopping.
But, unlike every other Tuesday, Blanca’s vegetable store was closed.
This minor setback disrupted my entire shopping experience. I was so upset. In my head, all there was were thoughts about how dare they close without letting me know and how I should probably start looking for a new vegetable place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Last Week Mindset - an analysis</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/59-quarantinemindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/59-quarantinemindset/</guid>
      <description>For someone whose first thought in the morning is setting the intention for a mindful day (however that wants to manifest itself that day) I found it fascinating how my mind has been residing in imagination this past couple of weeks. My last post is living proof of that. This quarantine, and the incapacity for action I feel due to the confinement has got me into self-centered loops of thoughts with a pretty obvious theme: wanting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30&#43; days</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/55-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/55-streak/</guid>
      <description>Postcards from the cushion </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎓 Buddhism and Modern Psychology</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/47-moocbuddhism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/47-moocbuddhism/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely loved this course. Robert Wright is a funny guy and his way of delivering hard concepts is pretty good. The course tries to bring together the Naturalistic (sometimes called Secular) notions of Buddhism under the scientific framework of Modern Evolutionary Psychology.
My grade was 95%
I&amp;rsquo;m obssesed with my newly found bitmojis</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doppelgänger</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/46-doppelganger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/46-doppelganger/</guid>
      <description>Recent studies have shown that dogs adopt some personality traits of their owner.
Every morning after watching my little Buddha contemplate the Truth of impermanence from his favorite spot in the balcony, I wonder if the opposite can be true.
April 21st, Colegiales, Argentina</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anicca</title>
      <link>https://addahna.com/blog/45-annica/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addahna.com/blog/45-annica/</guid>
      <description>the state or fact of lasting for only a limited period of time. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>