<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MOOC on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/mooc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MOOC on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with 💚 by Mica, 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/mooc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Success</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/60-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/60-success/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished the Success course offered by Wharton and all I can say are positive things about it. This course was great. The content in itself might not be mind-blowing (at the end of the day we all know that there’s an inner and outer sphere of success), but the exercises provided by Richard Shell, the instructor were poignant. They kept me thinking in these topics even after the lecture was done, and sparked pages of introspection in my morning journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎓🎓 The Science of Well-Being</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/48-tswb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/48-tswb/</guid>
      <description>This quarantine was all about happiness, self- improvement, and habits. Yesterday I officially completed Yale’s most popular class ever and my 2nd (actually 3rd) Coursera course during the COVID19 lock-down, The Science of Well-Being.
I enjoyed the course so much, that I enrolled in the UPenn Foundations of Positive Psychology Specialization and already audited Part I. It is a long course lasting a total of 10 weeks, I manage to complete it in 5 weeks by bingeing the first week through all the lectures and leaving the last 4 weeks for the Final Reweirement Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎓 Buddhism and Modern Psychology</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/47-moocbuddhism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/47-moocbuddhism/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely loved this course. Robert Wright is a funny guy and his way of delivering hard concepts is pretty good. The course tries to bring together the Naturalistic (sometimes called Secular) notions of Buddhism under the scientific framework of Modern Evolutionary Psychology.
My grade was 95%
I&amp;rsquo;m obssesed with my newly found bitmojis</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>