<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>quarantine-journal on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/quarantine-journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in quarantine-journal on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Micaela Ninni © {2020}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/quarantine-journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another day...</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/anotherday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/anotherday/</guid>
      <description>...another Peloton challenge failed,another meditation streak lost. home-made bread, the cause
BEGIN AGAIN
...and a Taylor Swift&#39;s Folklore is coming out tonight...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on repeat (forever)</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/folklore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/folklore/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Ted &amp; Joe</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/ted-and-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 07:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/ted-and-joe/</guid>
      <description>For the last year or so I&amp;rsquo;ve been witnessing the unfolding of the United States&amp;rsquo; presidential election. NYT articles, debates, Friday&amp;rsquo;s Shields and Brooks analysis on PBS, Bill Maher, Sam Harris, you name it I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to it all. From the, at one point, 25 nominees of the Democratic Party only Biden is standing.
Ted is very happy about this fact. Although it would have never been his (or probably anybody&amp;rsquo;s) first choice, he seriously believes Biden is the one that will defeat Trump in November.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Had to Start Somewhere</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 07:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/day1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco and Twain</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/sfand-twain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/sfand-twain/</guid>
      <description> “The coldest winter I ever spent was a summer in San Francisco.”
   Mark Twain   A year ago</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#0.5 Healthy habits</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/73-healthy-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/73-healthy-habits/</guid>
      <description>I was planning on doing an entire month for my vitality category, but I changed my mind. These are the chief pillars for a healthy life and I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to implement them throughout the quarantine with varying degrees of success depending on the week.
In order not to get too overwhelmed I will add these important having in pairs every week. I have a small headstart, as my yoga practice is well established already (Ashtanga Primary Series 5 times a week) and, I&amp;rsquo;ve been meditating on and off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Prayer</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/70-aprayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/70-aprayer/</guid>
      <description>For a sennight, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to design the blog I wanted. And deep down I know that day is today that website is going to be deployed into the world-wide-web.
This is an orison to the HUGO-Gods. All this work is not to be in vain. A command shall appear before I and addhana will go live.
So please almighty-HUGO, listen to this prayer, and provide the solution to this predicament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Project</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/68-thp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/68-thp/</guid>
      <description>Quarantine has been a rediscovery of Dan Harris and his 10% happier project. I’ve attended all his live meditations (while they were running), enrolled in the TPH app, and I’ve been listening to his podcast almost daily. His book (10% happier) was the first audiobook I listened to in the theme of meditation and Buddhism. I was living in Mexico, just recently started dating Ted and I was open to trying new ways to improve my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attachment</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/67-attachment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/67-attachment/</guid>
      <description>Like every Tuesday morning, yesterday I woke up early, kiss Frankie, and after an hour of journaling, I went grocery shopping.
But, unlike every other Tuesday, Blanca’s vegetable store was closed.
This minor setback disrupted my entire shopping experience. I was so upset. In my head, all there was were thoughts about how dare they close without letting me know and how I should probably start looking for a new vegetable place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peloton Challenge</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/66-pelotonchallenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/66-pelotonchallenge/</guid>
      <description>Moving to the States is exciting for several reasons: Christmases are going to be snowy, and Thanksgiving dinners will have turkey again. But most importantly the amazing world of online shopping will be at our feet and God I’m looking forward to it.
With the COVID situation and the unsafeness associated with close contact activities, we decided the first purchase to be a peloton bike. But in order to make things a little bit more fun, we decided to add a small challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnecting</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/65-reconnecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/65-reconnecting/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I (finally) graduated from college. After years of hard work with countless hours with my butt in the chair and my nose between textbooks, I made it over 5 years of intense work, all summarized in a 40-minute presentation.
Many of my close friends gathered to see the whole thing unfold in youtube, and reading their comments and feeling their virtual presence had a nice comforting sensation in a time where the sense of isolation is the new norm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 30th. The next day</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/64-june30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/64-june30/</guid>
      <description>Today I’m feeling pretty much like Jack Konfield’s book tittle
After the ecstasy, the laundry Or like the fish in the final scene of Finding Nemo, looking around wondering
“now what?”
My undergraduate education concluded yesterday (I’m finally a licenciada), and today life’s goes on, with quarantine more strict than ever and lifting the garlands from the floor.
Nonetheless I’ve never felt luckier to be surrounded by so many amazing people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Gentleman in Moscow - book review</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/63-agim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/63-agim/</guid>
      <description>“if a man does not master his circumstances then he is bound to be mastered by them.”
   Count Alexander Ilyich Rostov   ![bingo]/addhana(/63-AGIM.jpg)
Hotel Metropol, Moscow, Russia (circa 1905). Source Wiki Commons
It is hard finding someone that does not recommend ‘A Gentleman in Moscow‘, from my mother-in-law to my boyfriend and Bill Gates, Count Alexander Ilyich Rostov seems to have earned a place in everyone’s heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Through the Window</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/62-mornings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/62-mornings/</guid>
      <description>… Morning visitors ☀️ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bingo!</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/61-bingo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/61-bingo/</guid>
      <description>As part of my (many) quarantine challenges, I started playing Scrabble last week.
I’m not a natural. English is not my mother’s tongue and although I’ve always read a lot it was not until I had to sit for the GRE, and encountered the monstrous Verbal Section, that I made a conscious effort to expand my vocabulary.
The bright side of this whole endeavor is that there’s lots of room for improvement 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Success</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/60-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/60-success/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished the Success course offered by Wharton and all I can say are positive things about it. This course was great. The content in itself might not be mind-blowing (at the end of the day we all know that there’s an inner and outer sphere of success), but the exercises provided by Richard Shell, the instructor were poignant. They kept me thinking in these topics even after the lecture was done, and sparked pages of introspection in my morning journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Last Week Mindset - an analysis</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/59-quarantinemindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/59-quarantinemindset/</guid>
      <description>For someone whose first thought in the morning is setting the intention for a mindful day (however that wants to manifest itself that day) I found it fascinating how my mind has been residing in imagination this past couple of weeks. My last post is living proof of that. This quarantine, and the incapacity for action I feel due to the confinement has got me into self-centered loops of thoughts with a pretty obvious theme: wanting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Week Mindset</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/58-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/58-mindset/</guid>
      <description>I wish I there was no COVID; I wish there was no quarantine; I wish it hasn’t been extended two more weeks; I wish I had bought a sewing machine a couple of months ago; I wish I could have all the right colors of yarn to crochet all the amigurumi in Pica Pau’s latest book; I wish I would have started learning to weave, now I do not have a loom; I wish I was in Mexico; I wish I was in Malta; I wish I was in the Philippines or maybe Bali; I wish we were already in Philly; I wish I could have been with my grandad in his birthday (May 16th); I wish I can be with my brother in his birthday (June 19th), at least I was able to be with Ted in his birthday (April 29th); I’ll probably be able to be with my mum in her 50th birthday, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinnamon Rolls</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/57-cr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/57-cr/</guid>
      <description>Today was the first time in 66 days of quarantine that I cooked something other than a salad (needless to say I think is the first time I attempted to use the oven in 2 years since we moved here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandiculations</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/56-pandiculations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/56-pandiculations/</guid>
      <description>then and now  2017 – No formal yoga practice and obviously not scared of touching the floor in a random place in Mexico
  2020 – Ashtanga Quarantine practice in my dark room
  pandiculation (noun) – a stretching and stiffening especially of the trunk and extremities
   Merriam Webster   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30&#43; days</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/55-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/55-streak/</guid>
      <description>Postcards from the cushion </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Earth in a Poem</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/54-teiap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/54-teiap/</guid>
      <description>We say that you cannot divert the river from the riverbed. We say that everything is moving, and we are part of this motion, that the soil is moving, that the water is moving. We say that the earth draws water to her from the clouds. We say the rainfall parts on each side of the mountain like the parting of our hair, and that the shape of the mountain tells where the water has passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Anger</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/53-onanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/53-onanger/</guid>
      <description>For my granddad. Happy 86th Birthday A couple of valuable lessons became evident after my grandma bashed to me over the phone the other day:
  #1. Her anger and mistreatment reflect nothing about me but everything about her. And more importantly, it is impersonal.
  #2. Non-engagement in violent speech is the best tool to dismembering the anger you are receiving from the other side. When two people are acting mean to each other it’s a fight but, when only one of the parties is involved it’s just a crazy person yelling over a phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streak</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/52-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/52-streak/</guid>
      <description>… and 5 thoughts on intermittent fasting (IF)  I.F. really help with my morning-crush. When I’m not fasting, after breakfast I experience low energy where I could think of is crawling back to bed. IF has really helped me with the morning crush, allowing me to be more productive and have a more energy-stable day Because I break my IF with a big healthy lunch, I’m less incline to take little snacks through out the day (although yesterday after a toxic conversation with my grandmother I ate half a carrot budín).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Lessons</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/51-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/51-lessons/</guid>
      <description>1. When ordering ice cream it is important to only order fruit flavors or cream flavors. The mixture of the two is considered heresy. 2. Always read a book from cover to cover. You do not know what wisdom gems might be awaiting at the very end. 3. When your motives are unclear, is always better not to act. They might became apparent when emotions have settled. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fasting</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/50-fasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/50-fasting/</guid>
      <description>Since Sunday I’ve began intermittent fasting.
I’m using a great app, Zero, to track the 16:8 cycle.
Chores have been distributed the following way during the past couple of weeks of quarantine:
Mica – lunch Ted – dinner Since Monday Ted asks me (anxiously) around noon when I’m going to take care of lunch. Because of the 16 hour fast window, lately it has been around 2 o’clock, failing to realize this fundamental truth about our new lunch schedule:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling quesosa</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/49-quesosa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/49-quesosa/</guid>
      <description>In the past months I went from being the happy state of singletown to the happy silly state of ‘Hey! This is my boyfriend. Have I told you he is the most amazing person in the world (yes, probably like a thousand times)
  Being in love is like that – silly, inexplicable
  It simply just happens
  Sometimes we do look for it a little bit under some random rocks we encounter in our journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎓🎓 The Science of Well-Being</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/48-tswb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/48-tswb/</guid>
      <description>This quarantine was all about happiness, self- improvement, and habits. Yesterday I officially completed Yale’s most popular class ever and my 2nd (actually 3rd) Coursera course during the COVID19 lock-down, The Science of Well-Being.
I enjoyed the course so much, that I enrolled in the UPenn Foundations of Positive Psychology Specialization and already audited Part I. It is a long course lasting a total of 10 weeks, I manage to complete it in 5 weeks by bingeing the first week through all the lectures and leaving the last 4 weeks for the Final Reweirement Challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎓 Buddhism and Modern Psychology</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/47-moocbuddhism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/47-moocbuddhism/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely loved this course. Robert Wright is a funny guy and his way of delivering hard concepts is pretty good. The course tries to bring together the Naturalistic (sometimes called Secular) notions of Buddhism under the scientific framework of Modern Evolutionary Psychology.
My grade was 95%
I&amp;rsquo;m obssesed with my newly found bitmojis</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doppelgänger</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/46-doppelganger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/46-doppelganger/</guid>
      <description>Recent studies have shown that dogs adopt some personality traits of their owner.
Every morning after watching my little Buddha contemplate the Truth of impermanence from his favorite spot in the balcony, I wonder if the opposite can be true.
April 21st, Colegiales, Argentina</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anicca</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/45-annica/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/45-annica/</guid>
      <description>the state or fact of lasting for only a limited period of time. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/44-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/44-fall/</guid>
      <description>Leaves budge to the autumn zephyr  pervading the sepia sky  with dances and swirls  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papañca</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/43-papanca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/43-papanca/</guid>
      <description>Papañca is the Pali term used to describe the tendency of the mind to spread out from and elaborate upon any sense object that arises in experience, smothering it with wave after wave of mental elaboration, most of which is illusory, repetitive, and even obsessive, which effectively blocks any sort of mental calm or clarity of mind.
   Lion’s Roar Website
 This was my intended name for the blog, I end up choosing Addhana</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micaism</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/42-micaism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/42-micaism/</guid>
      <description>micaism   /ˈmʌɪkəˈɪz(ə)m/
  noun
 a deep understanding of the difference between the relative and absolute levels of Truth.   like in &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;hellip; but no&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multitasking</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/41-multitasking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/41-multitasking/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered my boyfriend can actually do two things at the same time.
Which ones, I rather not say</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>