<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>quote on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/quote/</link>
    <description>Recent content in quote on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with 💚 by Mica, 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/quote/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Second Kind of Impossible</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/105-quasicrystals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/105-quasicrystals/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I had learned early on to pay close attention whenever an idea is dismissed as “impossible.” Most of the time, scientists are referring to something that is truly out of the question, like violating the conservation of energy or creating a perpetual motion machine. It never makes sense to pursue those kinds of ideas. But sometimes, an idea is judged to be “impossible” based on assumptions that could be violated under certain circumstances that have never been considered before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Full Moon</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/full-moon-ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/full-moon-ba/</guid>
      <description>Three things cannot be long hidden: the Sun, the Moon and Truth
  The Buddha
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Earth in a Poem</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/54-teiap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/54-teiap/</guid>
      <description>We say that you cannot divert the river from the riverbed. We say that everything is moving, and we are part of this motion, that the soil is moving, that the water is moving. We say that the earth draws water to her from the clouds. We say the rainfall parts on each side of the mountain like the parting of our hair, and that the shape of the mountain tells where the water has passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raqnon</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/34-raqnon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/34-raqnon/</guid>
      <description> Your task is not seek for love, but merely to seek and find all the barriers within yourself that you have built against it
  Rumi – ‘Why Buddhism is true’
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunrise &amp; coffee</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/32-sunrisecoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/32-sunrisecoffee/</guid>
      <description> The meaning of life is just to be alive. It is so plain and so obvious and so simple. And yet, everybody rushes around in a great panic as if it were necessary to achieve something beyond themselves
  Alan Watts
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind Giants</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/27-windgiants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/27-windgiants/</guid>
      <description>La ventura va guiando nuestras cosas mejor de lo que acertáramos a desear; porque ves allí, amigo Sancho Panza, donde se descubren treinta o pocos más desaforados gigantes, con quien pienso hacer batalla y quitarles a todos las vidas, con cuyos despojos comenzaremos a enriquecer, que esta es buena guerra, y es gran servicio de Dios quitar tan mala simiente de sobre la faz de la tierra
  Don Quijote de la Mancha – capítulo VIII</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>