<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Penn on Addhana</title>
    <link>https://addhana.com/tags/penn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Penn on Addhana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with 💚 by Mica, 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://addhana.com/tags/penn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>StormAid</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/108-stormaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/108-stormaid/</guid>
      <description>In another chapter of Mica-Designs, a fellow graduate student ask me to help her design a logo for raising funds for a Hurricane Relief Fund for Central America.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on and off with these ones for the past couple of weeks, not really knowing what Nati wanted or finding sources of inspiration on Google. These are the ones I ended up picking for her :)
Gambit&amp;rsquo;s Front Page, here I go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being on the good side of statistics</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/104-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/104-covid/</guid>
      <description>Despite all the uncertainty surrounding COVID, we have sufficient evidence to show that death rates among young adults are pretty low. It is possibly even lower if the individual has no pre-existing conditions (like asthma or some auto-immune disease). But even with a death-rate of 0.1% is 500% more than the one we observe in the regular flu-season (0.02%).
I know I am on the good side of statistics. If, by any chance, I get COVID, there&amp;rsquo;s a big chance I end up having only mild symptoms and no severe, long-lasting effects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduate Mantra</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/103-dummest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/103-dummest/</guid>
      <description>From the dummest person in the class,the biggest piece on wisdom... You know what they call the dumbest person to graduate with a phd? Doctor. avocadontfckntalk2me
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committee, maybe?</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/102-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/102-committee/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the best description I found on how to write an email to a prospect member of your graduate committee in the middle of a global pandemic:
&#34;Hey I just met you.And this is crazy.
But here&#39;s my number
Committee, maybe?&#34;
But the good news even with all that ackwardness 3 out of 5 have already accepted. One if from New Zealand :)
I&amp;rsquo;m counting on you Doug and Ileana!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best case for Atheism</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/101-atheism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/101-atheism/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;I believe in the scientific method, and in the scientific method if you cannot test a hypothesis then you cannot reach a meaningful conclusion that is true&amp;rdquo;
 Elon Musk
Interview with Alex Friedman</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post 100th! - Official</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/100/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/100/</guid>
      <description>The small things that make me feel part of a larger community. I&amp;rsquo;m so proud :)
EES Profile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regrouping</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/99-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/99-fall/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in the midst of our daily routine, we simply forget to breathe.
To breathe and look around us. To realize that we are exactly where we want to be. That all the work we are putting in will eventually pay off, the same way it paid off in the past, which got us to the place we are right now - drinking mate, thousand miles away from home, and going through my favorite season for the second time this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EES Logo</title>
      <link>https://addhana.com/blog/99-eeslogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addhana.com/blog/99-eeslogo/</guid>
      <description>The Earth and Environmental Science Department is holding a contest for its logo. I have so much fun doing these kinds of things I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop myself from participating.
These are my two contributions to the contest:
 #fingerscrossedThe colors I used are Penn&amp;rsquo;s colors accoridng to these guidelines. Penn Name Font – Perpetua or Traveling Typewriter (free font here). EES Font - National Park (free font link here).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>